<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ben&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://benrosen.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ben&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 13:32:50 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://benrosen.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Random Color Pair</title>
      <link>https://benrosen.github.io/posts/random-color-pair/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 13:32:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benrosen.github.io/posts/random-color-pair/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a tiny little script that gives you two colors: one dark and one light.
I needed an easy way to create pairs of colors that were distinct enough to be used for foreground and background colors.
Right now, this package uses randomcolor to generate colors. randomcolor allows you to specify luminosity when generating colors, so I just generate one &amp;lsquo;light&amp;rsquo; color and one &amp;lsquo;dark&amp;rsquo; color and return the results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phaser React Tools</title>
      <link>https://benrosen.github.io/posts/phaser-react-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2020 09:22:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benrosen.github.io/posts/phaser-react-tools/</guid>
      <description>I spend a lot of time at work helping people who are new to game development. There are many excellent options for beginners who are interested in creating games, from Scratch to processing to Unity. These days, one of my favorite ways to make games is with Phaser. Phaser is easy to set up, and it has lots of great examples to work from. Phaser also has plenty of convenient features that make other game engines (looking at you, Unity) seem kind of clunky in comparison.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pixel Art Chess Pieces</title>
      <link>https://benrosen.github.io/posts/pixel-art-chess-pieces/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 20:37:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benrosen.github.io/posts/pixel-art-chess-pieces/</guid>
      <description>I worked as a host at a fancy restaurant for a few months right after highschool. During slow shifts, I would do chess puzzles to pass the time. The book of puzzles I had was huge. I guess I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a phone yet because I remember lugging that giant hardcover book to work on my bike every day. It was a workout.
Anyway, I recently got back into chess when some of my students discovered the game for the first time through Twitch.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
